Brother, show me the firecrackers.
Brother, go inside.  Show the firecrackers to Success Bhaiya.   Come on.
Yes brother, what do you want?
Madam, please take out the biggest rocket packet.
Also take out a big packet of pomegranate.
Here you go brother, these are your pomegranates too.
Madam, can I ask you something?
Yes, ask.
What is your salary?
₹10,000.
Madam, do you get Rs 10,000 in this era of inflation
?
Brother, it is not enough but I
earn more than this.   What does
earning more mean?  Hey, when the owner is not there, I
steal Rs 500 from the cash box.
Okay
brother, I have made the payment to madam.
Their success paid off.
Otherwise where should I get the payment?
What are you talking about madam?  I'll show you in a minute.
Look
madam, I have already made the payment to you.
Look at this.
Hey, whenever the rich lady is there, I
steal Rs 1000-500 from the cash box.   Did it.
Look at my pride.  I haven't talked nonsense since yesterday.   take
my struggle